I don't understand your objections,
Professor Goldfarb.
Why wouldn't the Sonora Desert
make a perfectly good Promised Land?
(Leonard:)Go away.
We could call it Nuevo Jerusalem.
(Goldfarb:)Please go away.
Said Pharaoh to Moses.
(Gablehouser:)Why are all these young women here?
(Leonard:)It's Take Your Daughter to Work Day.
Really? I was not aware of that.
(Raj:)Oh, yes.
There was a very official e-mail...
(Raj:)...that was sent to everyone
whose files indicated...
(Raj:)...they had daughters
between the ages of 14 and 16.
(Leonard(in a Yoda voice):)Hmm.
- Smooth.
- Thank you.
(Gablehouser:)There's the man of the hour.
So we have a socially awkward genius in
a room of attractive age-appropriate women.
All he has to do is hook up with one.